https://www.riedel.net/data-privacy/

Services
We provide a comprehensive suite of services to help you get the most out of your investment before, during, and after the sale.
ConsultingSupportContact our Technical SupportDownloadsBrochures & data-sheets, forms & tools, manuals & application notes, certificatesAcademyWarrantyRepairs
ContactAustraliaAustriaChinaFranceGermany HeadquartersJapanNetherlandsRussiaSingaporeSpainSwitzerland & ScandinaviaUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaTerms and ConditionsData PrivacyDisclaimer
Data Privacy
Privacy PolicyProtecting your personal data during the collection, processing and use of personal data when you visit our website is important to us. Your data is protected in accordance with statutory provisions. In the following, we would like to inform you about the nature and scope of the processing of personal data through this website in accordance with Article 13 of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).   I. Information on the responsible controller Riedel Communications GmbH & Co. KG Uellendahler Straße 35342109 WuppertalTel.: +49 (0) 202 – 292 - 90 E-Mail: marketing@riedel.net   II. Information on the data protection officer Our external data protection officer is happy to answer any questions about data protection: Mr Arndt Halbach, GINDAT GmbH Wetterauer Str. 6, 42897 Remscheid Email: datenschutz@riedel.netTel.: 02191 / 909 430   III. Data processing through the website Your visit to our website is recorded. We generally collect the following data that your browser sends to us:IP address currently used by your computer or your routerDate and timeBrowser type and versionOperating system of your computerWebpages you visitName and size of requested file(s)URL of referral website, if applicableThis data is only collected for the purposes of data security, improving our website offer and analysing errors on the basis of Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR. The IP address of your PC is only analysed in anonymised form (shortened by the last three digits). In all other respects, you are able to visit our website without providing information on your identity. We would like to point out that data transmission on the Internet (such as email communication) is subject to security vulnerabilities. It is not possible to completely protect data from access by third parties. Confidential data should therefore be sent to us by other means, such as by post.   Contact formPersonal data (such as your name, address data or contact details) which you voluntarily disclose to us, for example in connection with a request or otherwise, will be stored by us and only processed for correspondence with you and only for the purpose for which you have provided us with this data. This data is processed on the basis of Art. 6 (1) a) and Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR.  Registration on this website You can register on our website in order to access additional functions offered here. The input data will only be used for the purpose of using the respective site or service for which you have registered. The mandatory information requested during registration must be provided in full. Otherwise, we will reject your registration. To inform you about important changes such as those within the scope of our site or technical changes, we will use the email address specified during registration. We will process the data provided during registration only based on your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) DSGVO. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed. We will continue to store the data collected during registration for as long as you remain registered on our website. Statutory retention periods remain unaffected.   Newsletter We offer you the option to subscribe to a newsletter on our website. Your personal data is collected while registering for the subscription. You will first receive a confirmation email in order to ensure that you wish to subscribe to the newsletter with your email address. Only once you have clicked on the activation link contained in this email will you be included in our email mailing list and receive the newsletter. The newsletter subscription is recorded for documentation purposes (IP address, date and time). You have the option at any time to unsubscribe from the newsletter by sending us a corresponding message. In particular, you may also use the link at the end of each newsletter in order to unsubscribe. The legal basis is provided by Art. 6 (1) a) GDPR. To dispatch the newsletter, we use the newsletter service Rapidmail. This service provider only processes the data on our behalf and at our instruction in accordance with Art. 28 GDPR.   Secure data transmission In order to protect the security of your data during transmission, we use encryption techniques (SSL) via HTTPS, which accord with state-of-the-art technology.   IV. Recipients of personal data We may utilise service providers in connection with data processing in order to perform and execute processes. Specifically, we have involved service providers for the purposes of sending the newsletter and hosting our website. Contractual relationships are established with our service providers, which meet the requirements of Art. 28 GDPR; the contractual provisions contain the statutorily required points on data protection and data security.  V. Data collection by Google AnalyticsThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service by Google Inc. (‘Google’). Google Analytics uses ‘cookies’ – text files that are stored on your computer and enable analysis of your visit to the website. The information obtained by the cookie regarding your use of the website are generally transmitted to a Google server in the USA, where it is then stored. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR. In the event that IP anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will first be shortened by Google within the member states of the European Union or in other contractual states of the agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. We would like to point out that Google Analytics has been expanded on this website with the code‘anonymizeIp’, in order to ensure the anonymised collection of the IP address. Google uses this information on behalf of the operator of this website in order to analyse your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services relating to website use and Internet use to the website operator. The IP address transmitted by your browser in connection with Google Analytics is not combined with other data held by Google. You may prevent the storage of cookies by configuring your browser software settings accordingly; however, we would like to point out that, in this case, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Moreover, you may prevent the collection of the data obtained by the cookie relating to your use of the website (including your IP address) by Google as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available via the following link: tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR.   VI. reCAPTCHA To protect your requests submitted via online form, we use the service reCAPTCHA provided by the company Google Inc. (Google). This query serves to determine whether an entry has been made by a person or improperly by means of an automated machine program. The query involves the sending of the IP address and other data that may be required by Google for the reCAPTCHA service to Google. For this purpose, your entry is transmitted to Google, where it is further processed. Your IP address will first be shortened by Google within the member states of the European Union or in other contractual states of the agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. This service is performed on behalf of the operator of this website. The service is conducted on the basis of Art. 6 (1) Clause 1 f) GDPR.   VII. Google Maps This website uses the map service Google Maps via an API. The provider is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.In order to use the functions of Google Maps, it is necessary to store your IP address. This information is generally transmitted to a Google server in the USA, where it is then stored. The provider of this website has no influence on this data transmission. The use of Google Maps occurs in the interest of providing an attractive presentation of our website offers and allowing the user to find the locations indicated on our website more easily. This constitutes a legitimate interest in the meaning of Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR. If you do not agree to this processing of your data, you have the option to deactivate theservice of ‘Google Maps’ and to thereby prevent the transmission of data to Google. To this end, the JavaScript function in your browser must be deactivated. However, we would like topoint out that, in this case, you will only be able to use ‘Google Maps’ to a limited extent if atall. More information on the handling of user data can be found in the Google privacy policy: www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy   VIII. Social media YouTube Our website uses plugins from YouTube, which is operated by Google. The operator of the pages is YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. If you visit one of our pages featuring a YouTube plugin, a connection to the YouTube servers is established. Here the YouTube server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. If you're logged in to your YouTube account, YouTube allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account. YouTube is used to help make our website appealing. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of YouTube under www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy   Facebook-Plugins (Like & Share-Button) Our website includes plugins for the social network Facebook, Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA. The Facebook plugins can be recognized by the Facebook logo or the Like button on our site. For an overview of Facebook plugins, see developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/ When you visit our site, a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server is established via the plugin. This enables Facebook to receive information that you have visited our site from your IP address. If you click on the Facebook "Like button" while you are logged into your Facebook account, you can link the content of our site to your Facebook profile. This allows Facebook to associate visits to our site with your user account. Please note that, as the operator of this site, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted to Facebook or of how Facebook uses these data. For more information, please see Facebook's privacy policy at de-de.facebook.com/policy.phpIf you do not want Facebook to associate your visit to our site with your Facebook account, please log out of your Facebook account.   LinkedIn Our site uses functions from the LinkedIn network. The service is provided by LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Each time one of our pages containing LinkedIn features is accessed, your browser establishes a direct connection to the LinkedIn servers. LinkedIn is informed that you have visited our web pages from your IP address. If you use the LinkedIn “Recommend” button and are logged into your LinkedInaccount, it is possible for LinkedIn to associate your visit to our website to your user account. We would like to point out that, as the provider of these pages, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used by LinkedIn. More information can be found in the LinkedIn privacy policy at www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy   Instagram Plugin Our website contains functions of the Instagram service. These functions are offered by Instagram Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA. If you are logged into your Instagram account, you can click the Instagram button to link the content of our pages with your Instagram profile. This means that Instagram can associate visits to our pages with your user account. As the provider of this website, we expressly point out that we receive no information on the content of the transmitted data or its use by Instagram. For more information, see the Instagram Privacy Policy: instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/   Xing Our website uses features provided by the XING network. The provider is XING AG, Dammtorstraße 29-32, 20354 Hamburg, Germany. Each time one of our pages containing XING features is accessed, your browser establishes a direct connection to the XING servers. To the best of our knowledge, no personal data is stored in the process. In particular, no IP addresses are stored nor is usage behavior evaluated. For more information about data protection and the XING Share button, please see the XING privacy policy at www.xing.com/app/share   Twitter plugin Functions of the Twitter service have been integrated into our website and app. These features are offered by Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA.When you use Twitter and the “Retweet” function, the websites you visit are connected to your Twitter account and made known to other users. In doing so, data will also be transferred to Twitter. We would like to point out that, as the provider of these pages, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used by Twitter. For more information on Twitter's privacy policy, please go totwitter.com/privacyYour privacy preferences with Twitter can be modified in your account settings attwitter.com/account/settings   Google+ Plugin Our pages use Google+ functions. It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Collection and disclosure of information: Using the Google +1 button allows you to publish information worldwide. By means of the Google+ button, you and other users can receive custom content from Google and our partners. Google stores both the fact that you have +1'd a piece of content and information about the page you were viewing when you clicked +1. Your +1 can be displayed together with your profile name and photo in Google services, for example in search results or in your Google profile, or in other places on websites and advertisements on the Internet. Google records information about your +1 activities to improve Google services for you and others. To use the Google + button, you need a globally visible, public Google profile that must contain at least the name chosen for the profile. This name is used by all Google services. In some cases, this name may also replace a different name that you have used to share content via your Google account. The identity of your Google profile can be shown to users who know your email address or other information that can identify you. Use of collected data: In addition to the uses mentioned above, the information you provide is used in accordance with the applicable Google data protection policies. Google may publish summary statistics about users' +1 activity or share it with users and partners, such as publishers, advertisers, or affiliate websites.   Pinterest Plugin Our website contains functions of the Pinterest social network, operated by Pinterest Inc., 635 High Street, Palo Alto, CA, 94301, USA. When you visit a page containing the Pinterest social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Pinterest servers. The plugin transmits this log data to Pinterest servers in the United States. This log data may include your IP address, the address of the websites visited, which also includes Pinterest features, browser type and settings, the date and time of the request, how you use Pinterest, and cookies. More information about the purpose, scope and further processing and use of data by Pinterest, as well as your rights and options to protect your privacy, can be found in the privacy notices of Pinterest: about.pinterest.com/de/privacy-policy   IX. Use of cookies Cookies are used in our website offer. Cookies are small text files that are saved by your browser and stored on your computer. The use of cookies allows the website offer to be designed in a more user-friendly manner. For instance, it is possible to recognise the user for the duration of the session, without the user being required to constantly re-enter their user name and password. Cookies do not cause any damage to your computer and are deleted after your session is ended. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR. Some of the cookies we use are deleted directly after you close your browser (‘session cookies’).Other cookies remain on your terminal device and enable your browser to be recognised whenyou next visit the website (‘persistent cookies’). Data processing in connection with cookies, which only serve to facilitate the functionality of our website offer, occurs on the basis of our legitimate interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR. If you do not wish to use cookies, you can configure your browser to prevent the storage of cookies. However, please note that, in this case, you may not be able to use the full functionality of our websites.   X. Your rights According to Articles 15–21 GDPR, you may exercise the following rights with respect to personal data we store provided the relevant requirements of the GDPR are met. Right of access You have the right to access information about your personal data that we process. Right of rectification You are able to request the correction of incomplete or incorrectly processed personal data. Right of erasure You have the right to the deletion of your personal data, in particular on the basis of one of the following reasons:Your personal data is no longer required for the purposes for which it was collected or processed.You withdraw your consent on which the processing of your data was based.You have asserted a right of objection to processing.Your data was unlawfully processed.The right of erasure does not apply, however, if such deletion is opposed by the legitimate interest of the controller. For instance, this may include:Personal data that is required for the assertion, exercising or defence of legal claims.Deletion is not possible due to retention obligations.Insofar as data cannot be deleted, you may exercise a right to the restriction of processing (as follows).   Right to the restriction of processing You have the right to request us to restrict the processing of your personal data, if:You dispute the correctness of the data and we must therefore review the correctness.The processing is unlawful and you decline data erasure and instead request restriction of use.We no longer require the data, but you still need the data in order to assert, exercise or defend legal claims.You have submitted an objection to the processing of your data and it has not yet been determined whether our legitimate interests prevail over your interests.  Right of data portability You have the right to receive your personal data, which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly available and machine-readable format. Moreover, you have the right to have us transmit this data to another controller without hindrance by us, provided that the processing is based on a contract or consent, and our processing takes place with the aid of automated processes.   Right of withdrawal The data subject has the right at any time to submit an objection to the processing of their personal data, which takes place on the basis of Art. 6 (1) e) or f), for reasons arising from their particular situation; this also apples to profiling based on one of these conditions. Insofar as the processing of your personal data is based on a consent, you have the right to withdraw this consent at any time.   XI. Statutory deadlines for the erasure of data Insofar as no statutory retention obligation applies, the data shall be deleted or destroyed once it is no longer required for fulfilling the purpose of data processing. Various deadlines apply to the retention of personal data. For instance, data of tax relevance is generally stored for ten years, while other data is typically retained for six years in accordance with provisions under the Commercial Code. Furthermore, the storage period may also be determined by statutory limitation periods, which may generally amount to three years in the case of Articles 195 et seqq. of the Civil Code, for example, or in certain cases up to even thirty years.   XII. Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority In accordance with Art. 77 GDPR, each data subject has the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, if they believe that the processing of their personal data is in violation of the GDPR. The competent supervisory authority in data protection matters is the state data protection officer of the federal state in which our company has its registered office.   XIII. Disclaimer Liability for content As service provider, we are responsible for our own content on these webpages in accordancewith general laws (pursuant to Art. 7 (1) Telemedia Act, ‘TMG’). However, as serviceprovider, we are not obliged to monitor transmitted or stored external information or to investigate circumstances that indicate unlawful activity (Articles 8–10 TMG). This shall be without prejudice to obligations to remove or block the use of information according to general laws. Liability in this connection is only possible from the time we receive knowledge of an actual violation of the law. We will immediately remove the relevant content as soon as we become aware of corresponding violations of the law.  Liability for linksOur offer contains links to the external websites of third parties, over whose content we have no influence. For this reason, we are unable to accept any liability for this external content. The respective provider or operator of the website is always responsible for the content of the linked webpages. The linked webpages will be reviewed for possible violations of the law at the time of linking. Unlawful content could not be found at the time of linking. However, it is not feasible to review the content of the linked webpages on an ongoing basis, without specific indications of a violation of the law. We will immediately remove corresponding links as soon as we become aware of violations of the law.
Cookie-Declaration
HomeProducts & SolutionsIntercomDistributed Video NetworksApps for VideoFields of ApplicationSignal Contribution using JPEG-2000 or JPEG-XSMultiviewer AppIP AppProcessing AppManaged TechnologyOur SolutionsOur CustomersRental North AmericaNewsCompanyAbout usTrade ShowsMilestones & HistoryContactGermany (Headquarters)AustraliaAustriaChinaFranceJapanNetherlandsRussiaSingaporeSpainSwitzerland & ScandinaviaUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaEngineering HubsMontrealPortoViennaZurichCareerPupils & High-School GraduatesElectronics Technician for Devices and SystemsIndustrial clerkWarehouse Logistic SpecialistIT specialist in system integrationDual Study ProgramInternshipStudents & GraduatesStudent TraineeDirect entryJobsUnsolicited ApplicationRiedel's HR-TeamDownloadsCatalogue & UpdatesFirmware & SoftwareDatasheetsBrochuresCertificatesGuides & White PapersLogosServicesConsultingSupportAcademyWarrantyRepairsSkype TX STX-200  myRiedelContact SearchENDE
